我能怎么办
What am I gonna do?
找一群罪犯去打击另一群罪犯
Get a bunch of criminals together to fight the criminals?
这主意糟透了
That's a stupid idea.
好了  听着  计划是这样
Okay, guys. Game plan.
小丑已经把传送仪
Joker's taken the Projector
带到了韦恩庄园   韦恩庄园
to Wayne Manor. Wayne Manor.
是的   谢谢蝙蝠侠
Right. Thanks, Batman.
我们要找到那个传送仪   传送仪
We need that Projector. Projector.
否则我们就没办法
Or there's no way
把这些怪物炸回幽灵区
to blast these monsters... Monsters.
抓回幽灵空间   幽灵空间  对
...back to the Phantom Zone. Phantom Zone? Yep.
蝙蝠侠  我真的不需要你帮我完成
Batman, I really don't need you to finish my...
巨型城堡   不
Sand castles. No.
巨多的家庭作业   不
Sister's homework. No.
橘子汁儿   不
Succulent something. No.
大家注意
Um... Everybody?
蝙蝠侠在阿卡姆疯人院
Batman is in Arkham Asylum.